# ALEXANDRU STRAMBEANU

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

+1 (415) 528 0390 eugenalx@gmail.com linkedin.com/in/alexandru-eugen-strambeanu

Full Stack Developer with five years of experience leading both front-end and back-end development, and performing quality assurance. Led teams of 2-6 people across technology, business and design departments.

# SKILLS

PHP/Laravel

JavaScript/React

HTML5/CSS

Python

MySQL

Microsoft Office

## EDUCATION

#### International business law

Master's degree

Romanian-American University

**Bucharest** 

2005 - 2007

## Financial management

Master's degree

Romanian-American University

**Bucharest** 

2003 - 2005

# Management and marketing

Bachelor's degree

Romanian-American University

**Bucharest** 

1999 -2003

#### CERTIFICATES

PHP

SQL/MySQL

Python

Responsive Web Design

JavaScript Algorithms and Data Structures

# EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

# Full-Stack Developer

Dotbite, Vienna, Austria

June 2022 - December 2022

- Defined and developed the responsive presentation layer using HTML5, CSS3, PHP/Laravel, JavaScript/Vue.
- Tested websites across browsers, operating systems, and devices.
- Tracked and fixed bugs that were found during various phases of development.

## Web Developer

MaffBags, Bucharest, Romania December 2020 – February 2022

- Developed interactive e-commerce websites using PHP, JavaScript, MySQL, and Liquid.
- Defined and developed the responsive presentation layer using HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, and jQuery.
- Developed and implemented Shopify modules.
- Tested websites across browsers, operating systems, and devices.
- Tracked and fixed bugs that were found during various phases of development.
- Maintained, configured, and troubleshot servers.

#### Web Developer

Nazmie Edu, Bucharest, Romania

July 2017 - November 2020

- Developed interactive web application using PHP/Laravel and MySQL.
- Defined and developed the responsive presentation layer using HTML5, CSS3, PHP/Laravel, JavaScript, and jQuery.
- Tested websites across browsers, operating systems, and devices.
- Tracked and fixed bugs that were found during various phases of development.

## Quality Assurance Manager

Alexander Bake Shop, Bucharest, Romania

January 2014 – January 2018

 Oversaw operations of the finance department, set goals and objectives, and designed a framework for these to be met.

#### Financial Manager

Colts Farm & Food, Bucharest, Romania

February 2011 - January 2014

 Supervised and managed all operations of a mid-size retail store with heavy foot traffic.

### Financial Officer

JSI Research & Training Institute, Bucharest, Romania

August 2004 - December 2010

 Assured the integrity of the financial work products, processes, and procedures to safeguard the company's assets.